If you had said something earlier,
so many people wouldn't have been hurt.
I was afraid they would find me.
They are a bunch of animals.
We will go to the police tomorrow.
We can't let them call the police.
Who's there?
Siyao.
Yesterday...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You didn't get sick?
No.
I...
Ye Shi'an.
This is the police station.
Let me see, let me see.
Do you have a cold?
Where am I?
A hotel.
Why am I here?
You drank too much last night.
And it was raining heavily outside.
I could only bring you here.
You.
Come here.
Speak.
You won't bite or hit me, right?
Serves you right.
You long-faced sour pickle.
We are a man and a woman alone in a room.
Look at your clothes. I didn't touch them at all.
Aren't you being a bit greedy?
Then why are you dressed like that?
Who knows what you did to me?
Look and smell for yourself.
You drank too much last night and threw up all over my leg.
I kindly brought you here.
And you slapped me
and poked my eyes.
You little potato.
Do you have a conscience?
What did you call me?
Do you not want to...
Stop messing around.
We're going to be late for work.
That night,
I helped him escape from the winery.
After that, we didn't dare to show our faces.
We worked as coolies at the dock.
But we couldn't even get enough to eat.
So Wei Xiaodong finally fled back to the winery.
And then the rest happened.
So they are a group of people,
not just one or two, right?
Right.
They are a secret organization,
which includes many of the concession's
dignitaries and celebrities.
They are committing crimes collectively.
You must find their organization.
So the St. Faci Winery
is their stronghold.
Right.
They all have a
colorful banded krait tattoo.
But George didn't have that tattoo on him.
Impossible.
He had a tattoo on him.
I'm sure he did.
He was such an important witness.
Why wasn't he eliminated in advance?
I couldn't find him.
It was my mistake.
Read it to me.
What took you guys so long?
I overslept.
Overslept.
Why did you two come together?
It's you, Zhou Wei.
We bumped into each other at the door.
I read Zhao Bin's statement.
Let's talk about the case.
There's still one suspicious point.
When we went to the church that day,
we didn't see any tattoos on George.
Even if it was removed somehow,
it couldn't have left no trace.
Let's leave that for now.
Let's investigate Shengfaxi Winery first.
That Shengfaxi Winery
is different from other ordinary places in the concession.
High officials, dignitaries,
and celebrities from all walks of life frequent it,
so it's often guarded by patrolmen.
Even with orders from above, it might be difficult.
Then we'll investigate in secret.
We've already made enough noise.
If we get caught again,
it wouldn't be good to cause a diplomatic incident.
But that's the only clue.
We have to investigate.
Get ready for action.
Bai Weng, go to this place immediately
and protect Zhao Bin and his wife.
Young Master.
The person you asked me to look into,
I've found him.
No wonder
he looked at me in a special way.
Huang Xianzhong,
former chief of the police station.
He and the Master used to be classmates.
You now look very much like
the Master when he was young.
When you were a child,
he saw you.
Perhaps
he has already recognized you.
Young Master.
Don't go to the police station anymore.
It's too dangerous there.
Have you forgotten
how the Master died?
I will never forget
how my father died.
When he was brought back
from Shengfaxi Winery,
he was already dead.
He died of potassium cyanide poisoning.
I study chemistry
for this very reason.
Those people protect each other
and cover up the truth.
We are tucked away in a corner,
and it's already hard enough to hold onto Xinfeng Stronghold.
Bai Weng,
have you forgotten why I became a policeman?
Since I chose to be a policeman,
it's not just for revenge,
but to find out the truth
and clear my father's name.
Don't worry.
I will live a long and safe life.
I still have people to protect.
It's so late.
Where are you going?
Since when did you start caring about where I go?
Don't forget,
I am the head of the Huo family.
Right.
It seems you really didn't take
what I said to you before to heart.
This case cannot be investigated anymore.
Do you know something?
What you are doing now
is something the police department and the patrol station
strictly prohibit.
You're asking me what I want to know?
I only know that I'm worried about you.
Have you been to Shengfaxi Winery?
Where?
Shengwaxi.
Never.
What kind of filthy place is this?
Can you just stop getting involved with them?
Then tell me,
what do you think I should do?
You should be cultivating in the mountains.
In this Phoenix City,
be the head of the Huo family, the biggest merchant.
Your expectations of me
are very wrong.
Alright.
Say no more.
You can't go out tonight anyway.
Fine.
Why?
Can't I just be an ordinary daughter?
No.
Becoming the head of the Huo family is your destiny.
Becoming the protector of the Huo family is mine.
Keep an eye on her tonight.
Don't let her go out.
Miss,
don't make things difficult for us.
Get out.
Why isn't Huo Yining here yet?
Lord Huo probably won't let her come.
But that's for the best.
That's not right.
Given her personality,
she looks fierce,
but is actually full of righteousness.
No.
She must be in danger.
I have to go save her.
She's the head of the Huo family.
How could she be in danger?
Makes sense.
I understand Lord Huo.
Selfishly speaking,
I don't want her to take risks either.
Why is it so quiet?
Is she asleep?
Miss.
Oh no.
Inspector Zhou.
This trip to Shengfaxi Winery
is forbidden by both the police station and the patrol room.
You could very well lose your job over this.
If you want to leave,
I won't have any complaints.
If I were timid,
I wouldn't have gotten involved in the Jingxiang Society case.
However,
since Huo Yining isn't here,
on this journey to find the truth,
it will just be Superintendent Jiang and me, Zhou Wei.
In your dreams.
At a time like this,
how could you leave me out?
As long as my senior sister is here,
I, the little Taoist nun, will be here too.
Where's the little bandit?
I have other arrangements for him.
Let's go.
Oh no.
It's a trap.
Coming.
Mrs. Liu.
Has Siyao returned?
No.
She didn't come back last night.
This is bad.
Something happened.
Don't even think about getting out of here.
On charges of trespassing in the concession
and murder,
I will send you to the concession court.
Miss Jiang,
I told you that you would experience
a British prison.
It seems the Lord really blesses you.
Every step we take
can be anticipated by the other side.
There must be a mole.
But Li Chengrui
was not involved in this incident at all.
Who would have known we were coming to St. Faci?
That's because Mayor Zeng
explicitly forbade us from investigating.
Then,
we interrogated Zhao Bin at the police station.
Maybe at that time,
we were already being watched.
Then both Li Chengrui
and Mayor Zeng are suspects.
I'm sure
it's definitely a high-ranking official.
It's just that
we can't investigate anymore.
Locked up here,
we really can't get out.
Since you recognized me, Uncle Huang,
you should have guessed
why I became a police officer.
Nephew,
long time no see.
I thought your Duan family
had left Phoenix City,
gone far away,
and stayed out of worldly affairs.
After all,
when your father died,
that was what he hoped for.
His long-cherished wish
was to forge weapons more powerful
than those of the foreigners.
Unfortunately,
before it could be realized,
he passed away.
What he left behind,
I will carry out.
You've hidden for so long.
Why did you suddenly come to me today?
You know that
if Zeng Guoquan finds out you're still alive,
he will eliminate you completely.
Siyao and the others went to San Faci Winery last night
and are still missing.
My people can't find them either,
so I can only come to ask Uncle Huang for help.
Such a thing happened?
Okay.
I'll go ask around.